Welcome to this module, you made it through the course, you learned a lot about react and you're probably
Bu modle ho geldiniz, kurs boyunca yaptnz, tepki hakknda ok ey rendiniz ve muhtemelen
wondering what are the next steps.
bir sonraki admlarn ne olduunu merak ediyorsunuz.
Well obviously, next steps are what I mentioned right at the start of the course,
Tabii ki, bir sonraki admlar, dersin banda, pratikte,
practice, practice, practice.
pratikte, pratikte belirttiim admlardr.
You learned a lot about react and react as you learned has a lot of different concepts and things you
Tepki verdiiniz ve tepki verdiiniz iin rendiiniz birok farkl kavram ve eyle ilgili
can do with it.
ok ey rendiniz.
Now this course covered them, you now need to practice that,
imdi bu kurs onlar kapsyordu, imdi
so definitely dive back into some of the sections of this course,
bunu uygulamanz gerekiyor, bu yzden kesinlikle bu
pick the things which you might have already forgotten by now and practice them in projects you set
kursun baz blmlerine daln, imdiye kadar unutmu olabileceiniz eyleri sein
on your own. Set your own challenges, come up with demo projects you want to build, with popular apps you
ve kendi banza oluturduunuz projelerde aln. Kendi zorluklarnz belirleyin, oluturmak istediiniz demo projelerden yararlann, klonlamak istediiniz popler
want to clone and then just do it and practice the things you learned,
uygulamalarla yapn ve daha sonra sadece rendiiniz eyleri pratik yapn, baz
you'll hit some walls but I'm sure you can do it.
duvarlara arpacaksnz ama eminim ki bunu yapabilirsiniz.
Besides practicing, what else can you do,
Pratik yapmann yannda, baka ne
what makes sense?
yapabilirsiniz, ne mantkl?
Let's take a closer look over the next lectures.
Gelecek derslere daha yakndan bakalm.